<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:orientation="vertical">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:background="@color/dark_blue"
        android:orientation="vertical">
        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:textSize="36dp"
            android:textColor="@color/white"
            android:text="Terms and Conditions"
            android:layout_marginTop="30dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="30dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="30dp"/>
    </LinearLayout>
    <TextView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_margin="30dp"
        android:textSize="18dp"
        android:text="Terms and Conditions - United States\nFetch Consumers\nTerms and Conditions Agreement\nEffective: December 22, 2020\nPLEASE READ THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS CAREFULLY. THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS ('AGREEMENT') CONSTITUTE A LEGAL AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU AND Fetch, INC., A DELAWARE CORPORATION, AND ITS SUBSIDIARIES AND AFFILIATED COMPANIES, INCLUDING CAVIAR, LLC (COLLECTIVELY, 'Fetch','WE,' 'US,' OR 'OUR').\nSECTION 12 OF THIS AGREEMENT CONTAINS PROVISIONS THAT GOVERN HOW CLAIMS THAT YOU AND WE HAVE AGAINST EACH OTHER ARE RESOLVED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY CLAIMS THAT AROSE OR WERE ASSERTED BEFORE THE EFFECTIVE DATE OF THIS AGREEMENT. IN PARTICULAR, SECTION 12 SETS FORTH OUR ARBITRATION AGREEMENT WHICH WILL, WITH LIMITED EXCEPTIONS, REQUIRE DISPUTES BETWEEN US TO BE SUBMITTED TO BINDING AND FINAL ARBITRATION. UNLESS YOU OPT OUT OF THE ARBITRATION AGREEMENT: (1) YOU WILL ONLY BE PERMITTED TO PURSUE CLAIMS AND SEEK RELIEF AGAINST US ON AN INDIVIDUAL BASIS, NOT AS A PLAINTIFF OR CLASS MEMBER IN ANY CLASS OR REPRESENTATIVE ACTION OR PROCEEDING, EXCEPT AS SET FORTH IN SECTION 12(G); AND (2) YOU ARE WAIVING YOUR RIGHT TO SEEK RELIEF IN A COURT OF LAW AND TO HAVE A JURY TRIAL ON YOUR CLAIMS. THE ARBITRATION AGREEMENT COULD AFFECT YOUR RIGHT TO PARTICIPATE IN PENDING PROPOSED CLASS ACTION LITIGATION. PLEASE SEE SECTION 12 FOR MORE INFORMATION REGARDING THIS ARBITRATION AGREEMENT, THE POSSIBLE EFFECTS OF THIS ARBITRATION AGREEMENT, AND HOW TO OPT OUT OF THE ARBITRATION AGREEMENT.\n\n1. Acceptance of this Agreement\nFetch, including its wholly-owned subsidiary Caviar, provides an online marketplace connection, using web-based technology that connects you and other consumers, restaurants and/or other businesses and independent delivery contractors ('Contractors').  Fetch's software permits consumers to place orders for food and/or other goods from various restaurants and businesses, either for delivery or pickup (the 'Software'). Once a delivery order is made, the Software notifies Contractors that a delivery opportunity is available and the Software facilitates completion of the delivery to the consumer. Once a pickup order is made, the Software communicates with the customer regarding the availability of the order for pickup. Fetch is not a restaurant, delivery service, or food preparation business.\nIf you access any of our websites located at https://www.Fetch.com/ and https://trycaviar.com, install or use our Fetch or Caviar mobile application, install or use any other software supplied by Fetch, or access any information, function, or service available or enabled by Fetch (each, a 'Service' and collectively, the 'Services'), or complete the Fetch account registration process, you, your heirs, assigns, and successors (collectively, 'you' or 'your') hereby represent and warrant that: \n(a) you have read, understand, and agree to be bound by this Agreement; \n(b) you are of legal age in the jurisdiction in which you reside to form a binding contract with Fetch; and \n(c) you have the authority to enter into the Agreement personally and, if applicable, on behalf of any organization on whose behalf you have created an account and to bind such organization to the Agreement.\nThe terms 'User' and 'Users' refer to all individuals and other persons who access or use the Services, including, without limitation, any organizations that register accounts or otherwise access or use the Services through their respective representatives. Except as otherwise provided in this Agreement, if you do not agree to be bound by the Agreement, you may not access or use the Services.\n \n2. Modifications\nSubject to Section 12(k) of this Agreement, Fetch reserves the right to modify the terms and conditions of this Agreement or its policies relating to the Software or Services at any time, effective upon posting of an updated version of this Agreement through the Services. You should regularly review this Agreement, as your continued use of the Services after any such changes constitutes your agreement to such changes.\n\n3. Additional Terms and Policies\nBy using the Services, you agree to be bound by this Agreement and acknowledge and agree to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with Fetch's Privacy Policy, which is incorporated in this Agreement by reference. You also agree to abide by any additional Fetch policies for Users that are published on our website or mobile application.  Certain features of our Services may be subject to additional terms and conditions, which are incorporated herein by reference.\n\n4. Rules and Prohibitions\nWithout limiting other rules and prohibitions in this Agreement, by using the Services, you agree that:\n(a) You will only use the Services for lawful purposes; you will not use the Services for sending or storing any unlawful material or for deceptive or fraudulent purposes; and you will not engage in conduct that harms other Users, Fetch employees, or our community.\n(b) You will only use the Services in accordance with all applicable laws, including copyrights, trade secrets, or other rights of any third party, including privacy or publicity rights.\n(c) You will only access the Services using means explicitly authorized by Fetch.\n(d) You will not use another User's account, impersonate any person or entity, or forge or manipulate headers or identifiers to disguise the origin of any content transmitted through the Services.\n(e) You will not use the Services to cause nuisance, annoyance or inconvenience.\n(f) You will not use the Services, or any content accessible through the Services, for any commercial purpose, including but not limited to contacting, advertising to, soliciting or selling to, any Merchant, User or Contractor, unless Fetch has given you prior permission to do so in writing.\n(g) You will not copy or distribute the Software or any content displayed through the Services, including Merchants' menu content and reviews, for republication in any format or media.\n(h) You will not compile, directly or indirectly, any content displayed through the Services except for your personal, noncommercial use.\n(i) The information you provide to us when you register an account or otherwise communicate with us is accurate, you will promptly notify us of any changes to such information, and you will provide us with whatever proof of identity we may reasonably request.\n(j) You will keep secure and confidential your account password or any identification credentials we provide you which allows access to the Services.\n(k) You will use the Software and Services only for your own use and will not directly or indirectly resell, license or transfer the Software, Services or content displayed by the Services to a third party.\n(l) You will not use the Services in any way that could damage, disable, overburden or impair any Fetch server, or the networks connected to any Fetch server.\n(m) You will not attempt to gain unauthorized access to the Services and/or to any account, resource, computer system, and/or network connected to any Fetch server.\n(n) You will not probe, scan, or test the vulnerability of any system or network or breach or circumvent any security or authentication measures Fetch may use to prevent or restrict access to the Services or use of the Services or the content therein.\n(o) You will not deep-link to our websites or access our websites manually or with any robot, spider, web crawler, extraction software, automated process and/or device to scrape, copy, index, frame, or monitor any portion of our websites or any content on our websites.\n(p) You will not scrape or otherwise conduct any systematic retrieval of data or other content from the Services.\n(q) You will not try to harm other Users, Fetch, or the Services in any way whatsoever.\n(r) You will not engage in threatening, harassing, racist, sexist or any other behavior that Fetch deems inappropriate when using the Services. \n(s) You will report any errors, bugs, unauthorized access methodologies or any breach of our intellectual property rights that you uncover in your use of the Services.\n(t) You will not abuse our promotional or credit code system, including by redeeming multiple coupons at once or by opening multiple accounts to benefit from offers available only to first-time users.\n(u) You will not attempt to undertake any of the foregoing.\nIn the event that we believe or determine that you have breached any of the aforementioned, we reserve the right to suspend and/or permanently deactivate your account at our sole discretion.\n \n5. Contractors and Merchants Are Independent\nYou understand and agree that Fetch provides a technology platform connecting you with independent food service providers and others that provide the products offered through the Services ('Merchants'), and independent third-party contractors who provide delivery services ('Contractors'). You acknowledge and agree that Fetch does not itself prepare food or offer delivery services, and has no responsibility or liability for the acts or omissions of any Merchant or any Contractor. Merchant is the retailer; the services offered by Fetch pursuant to this Agreement do not include any retail services or any food preparation services. Fetch is not in the delivery business nor is it a common carrier. Fetch provides a technology platform facilitating the transmission of orders by Users to Merchants for pickup or delivery by Contractors. Fetch will not assess or guarantee the suitability, legality or ability of any Contractor or Merchant. You agree that Fetch is not responsible for the Merchants' food preparation or the safety of the food or whether the photographs or images displayed through the Services accurately reflect the food prepared by the Merchants and/or delivered by the Contractor, and does not verify Merchants' compliance with applicable laws or regulations. Fetch has no responsibility or liability for acts or omissions by any Merchant or Contractor. \nYou agree that the goods that you purchase will be prepared by the Merchant you have selected, that title to the goods passes from the Merchant to you at the Merchant's location, and that, for delivery orders, the Contractor will be directed by your instructions to transport the products to your designated delivery location. You agree that neither the Contractor nor Fetch holds title to or acquires any ownership interest in any goods that you order through the Services.\n"
        android:textColor="@color/black"/>
</LinearLayout>